

514-230-618



przemekleksa.atwebpages.com



linkedin.com/in/pleksa

przemyslawleksa@gmail.com



github.com/przemekleksa

# ABOUT ME

For many years I have been creating websites for friends, acquaintances and small companies. I finished IT studies with specialization in internet technologies with great scores. Lately I finished a Fullstack Developer Bootcamp. I would like to increase my web development skills by working with people that have more experience and knowledge than me.

# LANGUAGES

English C2

#### **INTERESTS**

Tarantino movies Motorsports First person shooter games

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO)).

# PRZEMYSŁAW LEKSA

#### **EXPERIENCE**

WEB DEVELOPER 2016 - present

Freelancer

Creating websites in HTML, CSS, JS, React, Redux, PHP, Bootstrap, jQuery. Setting up and modifying Wordpress and Prestashop pages. Using GIMP and Photoshop to create website layouts.

ORDER MANAGMENT COORDINATOR april 2019 - present

al.to (x-kom group)

Ordering products. Confirming clients orders. Close cooperation with product managers, chief executive officer, copywriters, contact center, warehouse staff and suppliers.

SENIOR COPYWRITER

al.to (x-kom group)

june 2016 - april 2019

Creating product presentation for online shop and auctions. Preparing products specifications. Training new employees. Setting up and management of department wiki help page. Highest employee evaluation score in whole department that employs 15 people.

WEB & E-COMMERCE SPECIALIST november 2015 - january 2016

Pink Parrot Media

Acquiring clients preferences and needs. Managing a team of developers. CMS systems support. Creating Content. Editing websites.

#### **EDUCATION**

COMPUTER SCIENCE

october 2012 - december 2016

Wyższa Szkoła Zarządzania i Bankowości w Krakowie

Specialization: Internet technologies

## **COURSES**

Codebrainers Fullstack Developer Bootcamp march 2019 - june 2019

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Javascript, React, Redux, jQuery, Python, Django, Flask, PHP, GIMP, Photoshop, Wordpress, Prestashop

## VOLUNTEERING

POLISH GROUP LEADER 2014 & 2015

**Erasmus+ Hungary** 

Participation in daily meetings with other countries leaders. Taking care of participants needs. Creating a friendly environment. Participation in analog photography and bike building workshops.